I'm going to let you speak, but let's not get the attitudes and stuff because you're my sister and I respect you.
I don't have an attitude. I'm being direct to you.
Domestic violence, women or men or even attack.
What is the first thing we say? It's like, you know what? It's not your what?
It's not your fault. So that's what we do.
We hold on to this narrative that, well, it's not our fault and the issues in our community, they're not in our fault.
And the white man needs to give us something.
The old white lady down the street is looking at me and I don't know why she got braids in her hair.
And we focus on all these other stupid things that don't matter.
We don't get to the root of the fact that we're killing each other at a higher rate than any other race.
It is self-hatred amongst us, I believe, that we can do that.
My cousin, my mom's cousin, excuse me, coming from the church parking lot and guess who stuck her up and robbed her at gunpoint?
A black man.
I need you to get to the point so I can respond.
My point is that, and I'm not trying to be funny, unless, like you said, we're going to keep it respectful.
Yeah, but you're monopolizing the whole conversation.
I'm not trying, okay, I'm going to let you speak, but let's not get the attitudes and stuff because you're my sister and I respect you.
I don't have an attitude. I'm being direct to you.
But how you talk to them, you're not going to talk to me.
And you're not going to do that with me either.
So you're stating your point and you've been stating your point for quite some time.
Do you have a reason for me to respond?
Yeah, would you allow me to respond? So that's a better response. Go ahead.
The response that I have for you is that everything you're saying does not exist in a vacuum.
I actually agree with you in that, yes, there has been an incredible denigration of black worth and black pride in this nation.
I think it's also very important to acknowledge what has contributed to that.
And to state that it is only black people that have contributed to that is a false flag.
So we have to admit that.
So in order to have this conversation around how we got here, you can't say, oh, well, we're caring about the white woman getting braids and that doesn't matter.
And this thing, all of that attaches.
All of that is actually a very big part of the lack of worth of black people.
I'll ask you, do you think we're resilient?
What does resilience mean to you?
Do you think we have to be perpetual victims?
Or do you think that black people are resilient?
I think that those are two different conversations.
I think they're because I think that the concept of black people being victims is really trying to not provide accountability to where the root problem for the actual cause is.
And if we keep saying that somebody is a victim and that that doesn't mean that the other person should have to have to actually have accountability, then what are we really doing?